wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Wait, is this okay?
Take a look at this.
Bulguribon is on Bulguribon.
Bulguribon on Bulguribon!
Good afternoon, everyone. I'm Yoshika Matsuda, from Tazuka 46.
I'm Hideo Kato. This is Kumi Sasaki.
Luster Luster... I think it's pretty obvious...
Today we're at Audrey's Escape Game in Tokyo Dome City!
Yay! Nice Wakabayashi-san!
He's so cute!
I wonder how she did it.
Mr. Wakabayashi...
Mr. Haruhi, too.
We're all here today.
Goods.
Packers.
And neck warmers.
Actually, it's a hair band.
But I have a new idea.
It was a little cold.
School test with the three sisters.
I went with black.
I'm in black, and you're in pink.
I'm going to go with
a little bit.
I used to be in the All Night Nippon event.
Mr. Black and Pink.
I see.
We're co-hosting.
Little Two's.
Yes, Little Two's.
Ryu.
Ryu too.
We have to start the escape game.
The opening has to be longer and longer.
We don't have another half hour.
It's true, Audrey's All Night Nippon
Audrey's All Night Nippon is 4 hours long out of 2 hours.
About 43 minutes.
It's usually the opening.
So let's talk for a while here.
Especially in Hinatazaka.
Little two's a crowd.
I'd like to take on today's challenge with the members
I'd like to take on today's challenge.
I look forward to working with you.
Okay, we'll start solving now.
Let's do it here.
Okabayashi-san.
Then, why don't the three of us listen together?
No, it's a pain in the ass.
Announcer Iida, can you explain the situation one more time?
Ladies and gentlemen... as reported in the news...
A state of emergency has arisen.
Toshiaki Kasuga of the comedy duo Audrey has shown up at Tokyo Dome City.
Toshiaki Kasuga of the comedy duo Audrey, has appeared in Tokyo Dome City and is currently manipulating the people of Dome City.
According to eyewitnesses, immediately after Mr. Kasuga uttered the word "tooth".
After Mr. Kasuga uttered the word "Toothless", people started to dance the "Kaskasu Dance" with empty eyes.
A bad situation.
Just before Mr. Kasuga appeared on the air, a message was broadcast in Japan
to solve the riddle if they wanted to stop Kasuga.
If you want to stop Haruhi, you have to solve the riddle.
Now, to all of you in Little Tooth who are listening to this program...
I'm going to reveal the email we received from the mysterious person.
If you find out anything, please send it to us.
Hey, Little Toothless.
Worst case scenario, I can hold the dome by myself.
But if there's anyone out there who thinks it'd be better if Kasuga was there too...
I'd like you to try and solve this mystery for me.
I'll do it.
I'm done listening.
Let's start with the written problems in this booklet.
Step 1.
A letter from a mysterious person.
I wonder who it is.
There might be a clue here.
I see.
Oh, this is so hard!
I found the answer.
You're early.
You're early, Captain.
Captain, you're early.
Even if you've never solved a riddle before.
I'm sure you'll be glad you listened to the radio.
Heh.
Are you done?
I'm done.
Oh, my God.
But I don't know if I got it right.
Let's all...
Yeah, let's check the answers.
Oh, this is fun!
Here it comes.
It's fun, isn't it?
There it is.
So we're just gonna put this in there?
This is it, right? That's it.
Sushi, too. Okay, I'll put it in.
Please, let's put it in. -We're in charge of the web.
Webmaster.
What? Why are there so many?
It's easy to stamp.
Cute!
Well, then, you're a very active type.
Shall we go? I'm going.
Go ahead. Go to the designated place.
I'm off. I'm on my way.
Zing, zing, zing.
More salt.
The sun is shining.
It's a beautiful day.
Not really.
There are four panels with the history of the Tokyo Dome.
This is it, isn't it? Yes, it is.
It says, "What's the smallest building? It says, "What's the smallest building?
I see it! I see it! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Can I drop this just in case?
This is fun.
This is awesome!
Look at this!
Oh, my God!
Isn't this amazing?
Oh, man, oh, man, oh, man!
This is fun.
It's amazing!
That's why I typed it in here.
Thank you.
Here we go.
There you go!
Wow!
This is so much fun!
Oh, here comes another audio opportunity.
Let's hear it for the audio chance!
It seems that in the next riddle
We need to hear from Mr. Kasuga's witnesses.
Can you hear me, Little Suses?
Yes, I can hear you.
Try to solve the next riddle.
Okay, let's go to the next one.
Two.
Oh, we're on the move again.
Let's go back to the north road, cross the bridge and go through the archway.
All right, let's head up.
Let's go up these stairs.
Okay.
Let's go!
One, two, three...
Mr. Kasuga's funny way of counting
I'll do 3 or something.
One Two Sancy
One-two-thousand-seven.
Then here's the sash
Page five, six.
Please.
I'm looking for all of them, right?
Where?
Over there, there was one.
I found him...
Please give it to me over there.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Just look at him.
This is a surprise.
Oh, I made a mistake.
So, I guess this is where the word "free" comes in.
Okay, let's go to the second one.
Oh, what a great panel!
Wow, Mr. Taniguchi?
You scared me.
Wow, oh, oh, oh, oh.
This one looks like panel 2, doesn't it?
I was walking toward Mr. Taniguchi, and suddenly everyone was like...
Mr. Taiga.
Great. Then I saw Mac.
Mr. Taniguchi!
Wow!
That's great.
You'll be in Special Week soon.
You'll be on Special Week.
Yes, at Taniguchi's company.
Wow.
Consecutively.
Yes, yes, yes.
And then you testified...
Like this, like this...
like this...
Let's type it into the web
Web time!
That's great!
Whoa! Correct!
Here's the audio again.
Let's hear it then.
Mr. Wakabayashi, we've got another mystery answer from Little Tooth.
Wow, there's such a brilliant guy in Little Tooth.
Well, that clears up the second riddle.
You're right, that's the end of it.
Mr. Wakabayashi, another new mail!
You've got to be kidding me, Hiroshi! Don't bring that e-mail.
Little Toothless, we honestly have no idea what's going on here.
Little Toothless is our only hope now.
You got it.
I'm glad I can count on you.
I'm pushing on.
Is it there?
Right there.
And then...
And then we'll move on to this area.
Mystery with the voice.
Okay, I'll just sit here on this bench.
I'll sit down.
Yes, sir.
There's a walkway to your left.
This one?
Not this one.
Mystery with audio.
There's a platform.
Gregory bomb.
Gregory.
This is too difficult.
I'm guessing this is how they put it.
I've never seen a Gregory bomb before.
Oh, man.
Oh, I made it!
Yay!
Let's hear the audio here.
It seems that Little Toothless has delivered another answer to the riddle.
Is this the end of this strange game?
What is Little Toothless' answer?
What's Little Toothless' answer?
It sounds like a phone call.
It's a phone.
Hello?
Wakamatsu, I'm here.
I'm stuck in a small room.
If you're listening to this, Little Toothless...
Continue to solve the mystery.
Yes, ma'am.
That's great, Mr. Satomichi... the white heart.
Amazing.
That's great.
There's a space for a safe.
Yes.
You must know a lot about the area around Tokyo Road.
I'm sure of it.
You won't get lost that day.
That's good.
Here's the safe.
Here's what I think.
Open it up to page 9 or 10.
Let's solve the mystery.
With these translation stickers.
You mean we're gonna put these on?
Yes, that's right.
This is it.
Oh.
Interesting.
Yay!
I did it.
It's an answer, so...
I got it right.
I like the safe number.
I opened it.
And then I got a piece of paper inside.
That's fun.
Shall I take it?
Thank you.
It's time for your call.
Let's make a call and get some information.
Got it.
I'm glad you got this number.
The answer to step 4-3 is...
Hang up the phone.
Hang up?
Or hang up.
If I'm told to hang up, I don't want to hang up.
But I have to hang up before he does.
I had to hang up on him.
Next.
Little Toothless, who solved the mystery.
I want you to head to this lab.
But we don't know what's in there.
You'll have to be very careful.
Yes, sir.
Shall we?
Let's go.
But the uniforms for everyone arrived at the office!
Eeeee...
No way!
The other day on All Night Nippon Zero
Mr. Ishii, the producer
Mr. Hikaru Ishii
Yes!
Mr. Hikaru Ishii gave it to me.
Aaaaah!
I sent it to the company as well.
Eeeee...
Thank you very much.
I would like to wear it with everyone.
If you go further down this road, there seems to be a laboratory.
Yes, sir.
Oh, isn't this it?
This is it.
Huh.
Heart.
Okay.
Oh.
I'm sorry I'm over it.
Oh!
I'm so surprised you could make it all of a sudden.
Okay, let's go in.
Once you're in, check out what's inside.
I'll take a picture of the panel with the instructions near the exit.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Wow!
Ehhhh...
Eh, wow.
I'm surprised.
You scared me.
Scary.
You scared me so much.
Your fingers are glowing.
You mean you're going to take a picture of this?
Hey, this is amazing.
I'll take a picture of this.
This Kasuga-san is amazing.
Look, there's no wrinkles.
Her forehead is wrinkled, too.
Almost... but not quite.
Let's get out of here.
Okay.
Bye bye, Mr. Kasuga.
Mr. Kasuga.
Oh, I found the answer here.
Byteuce.
I see.
Here it is.
Well, let's go outside and type it in.
What? You scared the shit out of me.
I'd like to go out with a bang.
You want me to type it in then?
Yes, please.
Do you want to do the whole thing?
Oh, there you go.
That answer.
Here we go again.
Mr. Wakabayashi, Little Tooth's email.
This one has a picture.
Is this Haruhi?
But something's wrong, isn't it?
There's a photo on SNS too.
What?
I'm creeped out.
Please push.
I see... we don't have to go here to solve it.
Back to where we started?
Sure, let's go.
Wow, that's great.
Amazing.
The sunrise.
If you're listening to the radio, you're in for a real treat.
It's going to be hot!
Let's do it right at the start.
This is No. 4.
Don't you think they're going to dismantle the beeswax?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's a bit...
I was a little sad.
It's not Otori Kasuga anymore.
No, Watachan.
That's not Otori Kasuga, is it?
No, it's not... you guys...
I need to drink some candy cane juice.
Oh!
Oh, it's done!
You got it!
Thank you for solving my riddle today.
Miffy-chan!
Miffy-chan
Miffy!
See you again later at the Tokyo Dome.
You made a mistake.
Real.
Adios
Adios.
I'm done solving the riddle.
Wow.
You're a fifth-rate student.
You really are.
So... we've successfully completed the escape game.
Yay!
We even walked by the Tokyo Dome.
I was even more excited!
A few more days
A few more days... I want them to come... but I don't want them to come.
I don't want you to come.
This is not the best time.
It's a fun time, you know, wearing all these goodies and stuff.
I'm just looking forward to it.
We're all going to Hiratazaka together.
I'm looking forward to having fun with everyone.